Hello, everyone. Welcome to this video. Before I go into this video, I'd just like to remind you of the context.
It's a bit boring, but this time I copied already the context, so it should be a bit faster.
So, previously, we did an introduction to the inter business interface,
and I showed you the basic methods of doing reasoning for the backward and substitution and induction of natural numbers.
And then I discussed with you how to deal with lists last week.
So, this was, I discussed recursive functions on lists and how we define them,
and then how we do proofs by structural induction on lists.
And then, in the last video, which is the first video for this week,
I discussed with the algebraic datatypes, how to define datatypes like natural numbers, lists, and trees,
which are the most interesting ones, trees.
So, in this video, what I'll be doing is recursion algebraic datatypes,
particularly, in fact, I should call it primitive recursion.
So, that's a proper terminology.
And, okay.